wonderoftech.com 2019-09-20

# Privacy Policy

**What information do we collect?**

We collect information from you when you register on our site, subscribe to email notifications of new articles, or leave a comment.

When commenting or registering on our site you may be asked to enter your: name, e-mail address and/or website address. You may, however, visit our site anonymously.

**What do we use your information for?**

The email address you provide may be used to send email notifications of published articles if you subscribe to The Wonder of Tech. The email address you provide for subscriptions or comments may also be used to send you information, respond to inquiries, and/or other requests or questions.

**How do we protect your information?**

We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you enter, submit, or access your personal information.

**Do we use cookies?**

Yes. Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computer’s hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information.

We use cookies to understand and save your preferences for future visits and compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future. We may contract with third-party service providers to assist us in better understanding our site visitors. These service providers are not permitted to use the information collected on our behalf except to help us conduct and improve our business.

**Do we disclose any information to outside parties?**

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

**Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance**

We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act), we do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website is directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older.

**Your Consent**

By using our site, you consent to our [online privacy policy](https://www.wonderoftech.com/privacy-policy/).

**Changes to our Privacy Policy**

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page, and/or update the Privacy Policy modification date below.

This policy was last modified on October 24, 2013.

**Contacting Us**

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below.

carolyn@wonderoftech.com
